recruitmilitary.com 2019-04-14

# Privacy | RecruitMilitary

RVET Operating DBA RecruitMilitary LLC (“RecruitMilitary”) has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of our users. Your privacy is very important to us. We want to provide a safe, secure experience for all of our users. Because we gather certain types of information about users of our site, we feel you should be aware of the terms surrounding the gathering and use of that information.

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT, AND HOW DO WE USE IT?

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

We collect personally identifiable information that you supply to us voluntarily through the use of our website, such as your name, résumé, personal references, career history, payment information, feedback, phone number, or email address.

We may use that information to respond to an email or other inquiry or request, to help improve our website or our services, to customize your experience using our website, or to send updates, electronic newsletters, text messages, or email notices about RecruitMilitary or the services we offer, which we believe may be of some interest to you. We may combine this information with other generally or publicly available information to help us identify the preferences or interests of visitors to our website.

In any email or text messages that you may receive, you will find an opt-out option you may utilize to stop receiving future messages by category type or all message types.

Subject to the restrictions described in the “Résumés” section below, we may share this information with client companies that utilize our service to place or hire candidates into specific job positions. Additionally, our parent company, Bradley-Morris, Inc., is a job placement firm placing military veterans into positions with companies. Bradley-Morris recruiters may contact you through their search activities on the RecruitMilitary website. If you have indicated that you have an interest in franchising, entrepreneurial, or educational activities, we may also share this information with client and affiliate companies who utilize our service for assisting candidates with such activities. We may also provide this information to companies that assist us in the provision of our services, including helping us fulfill your request for information or placement in a job position. Finally, we may share this information with select third party companies that may contact you directly with special and promotional offers for their goods or services.

We also reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information if: (1) the disclosure is necessary or useful to our provision of services; (2) we believe in good faith the disclosure is required by law (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order); (3) we believe in good faith the disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, interests, or property; or (4) we are acting in good faith to protect an individual’s personal safety.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose information about your individual visits to RecruitMilitary.com or your personal information to any outside parties.

### RÉSUMÉS AND PROFILES

If you submit your résumé and profile information to the RecruitMilitary online job board database, it will be viewable by potential employers and recruiting firms, and all employers and recruiters who have access to our résumé database will have access to your résumé. We use our best efforts to grant access to this database only to employers, educational institutions, franchisors, recruiters, hiring managers, headhunters, and human resource professionals, but cannot guarantee that other parties will not, without our consent, gain access to this database. You may remove your information from our searchable database at any time; however, parties who have access to the database may have retained a copy of your information, including your résumé and profile information, in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of résumés in these instances, or for the use or privacy of your information by any of such parties while résumés are in the database. Please be aware that the Department of Labor, Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs regulation at 41 CFR Part 60-1 (Obligation to Solicit Race and Gender Data for Agency Enforcement Purposes, also known as “Internet Applicant” rule), requires RecruitMilitary to maintain your records for a period of two years.

### COOKIES

To enhance your experience at RecruitMilitary, we use a feature on your Internet browser called “cookies”. Cookies are small bits of data that are written to your hard drive when you visit a website and that contain information such as a user or session ID to track the pages you’ve visited or a username and password so you don’t have to re-enter it throughout your visit. We use cookies, including third-party cookies such as Google Analytics, in the administration of our website in order to keep track of movement of an individual user from one screen to another, and to remember user names, passwords, user preferences. This information may be used by us to detect or resolve website problems, to assist with customer support issues, and to better understand how users visit our site. If you do not wish to share this information, please refer to the “Help” category on your browser’s toolbar for information on how to customize or disable cookies. Please be aware that you will not be able to use RecruitMilitary.com if you disable cookies in your browser.

### AGGREGATE INFORMATION

Like most websites, we automatically gather and log information about your computer and navigation patterns, including your IP address, browser type, operating system, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, the specific web pages that you visited during your connection to our website, and time/date information about your visit. We may use this information, in aggregate form, for system maintenance or to gain a better understanding of how our website is used. We share this information, in aggregate form, with third parties for research or marketing purposes. CONTROLLING AND UPDATING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION If you wish to change or correct your personal information, or “opt out” of receiving notices or updates sent by RecruitMilitary, you may log into your account and edit your profile information or change your settings.

### LINKED SITES

Other websites that you visit, including those linked from or to our website, may have separate privacy policies or no policy at all. Other websites may use personal information differently than our policy permits so we strongly encourage you to review the privacy policies of any site before you provide your personal information on the internet.

### DATA INTEGRITY AND SECURITY

We utilize information technology security to keep the information that you provide to us via our website secure. We also attempt to have privacy protection controls in place with our vendors in order to ensure that your personal information is protected from unauthorized access or disclosure. All of our employees must abide by our Privacy Policy. If an employee violates our privacy policies, he or she will be subject to our disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

RecruitMilitary is not designed to attract individuals under the age of 18. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe that RecruitMilitary has any information from or about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us at support@recruitmilitary.com.

### BUSINESS TRANSITIONS

If RecruitMilitary goes through a business transaction, such as a merger, acquisition, or asset sale, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. We will notify you via prominent notice on our website of any such change of ownership or control of your personally identifiable information.

### REVISIONS

RecruitMilitary reserves the right to periodically revise this policy. In the event we modify our policy, we will give reasonable notice. Since notice of any such policy change will not appear on our website indefinitely and may only be posted for a limited time, it will be incumbent upon you to check our Privacy Policy regularly to see if we have made any modifications.

You can contact us at:

RecruitMilitary LLC, ATTN: Privacy Issues 422 West Loveland Avenue, Loveland, OH 45140

Last Revised: January 31, 2017
